[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
Now that we've talked about Classification Error,
والآن فقد تحدثنا عن الخطأ في التصنيف،
we can explore the notion of Overfitting in classification.
ويمكننا استيضاح فكرة التطابق المفرط في التصنيف.
Before we start, let's review what we talked about when we discussed overfitting
وقبل أن نبدأ، دعونا نستعرض ما تحدثنا بشأنه عندما قمنا بمناقشة التطابق المفرط
the regression course.
في الدورة التدريبية الخاصة بالانحدار.
Going back to the regression course,
وبالعودة إلى الدورة التدريبية للانحدار،
we had this running example of where we're trying to predict
فسيكون لدينا مثال التشغيل، والذي حاولنا من خلاله التنبؤ
price of the house in the y axis given some features of the house.
بسعر المنزل في المحور Y، نظرًا لبعض ميزات المنزل.
In this case, the x axis is the square feet or the size of the house.
ويمثل المحور X، في هذه الحالة المساحة بالقدم المربع أو الحجم للمنزل.
And we see on the left here a really nice, smooth
ونرى على جهة الشمال هنا، منحنى سلس ورائع
curve that helps us predict what's the price for house given it's square feet.
والذي يساعدنا على التنبؤ بسعر المنزل نظرًا لمساحته بالقدم المربع.
However if instead of using a second degree polynomial like we did on the left,
ومع ذلك، وبدلاً من استخدام حدود من الدرجة الثانية كما فعلنا على جهة الشمال،
we use a higher or lower polynomial we might get a really crazy wiggly line that
واستخدمنا حدًا أعلى أو أسفل الحد، لذا قد نحصل على خط متلوي ومضطرب
fits the training data extremely well but doesn't generalize beyond the training
والذي يتناسب مع بيانات التدريب تمامًا، ولكن لا يعمم ليتجاوز
data to data in the test set or in the truth in the real world.
بيانات التدريب إلى البيانات في مجموعة الاختبار أو تلك الحقيقية في العالم الواقعي.
so in this case we say that the model F here has over-fit the training data.
ولهذا نقول في هذه الحالة إن النموذج F هنا به تطابق مفرط لبيانات التدريب،
Now in classification, we going to have the same kinds of problems and
وسنحصل في عملية التصنيف على نفس الأنواع من المشكلات
we're going to have to try to address it.
وسنحاول الحصول عليها لاستعراضها.
What happens when you learn the model, which is too good on the training data
ماذا يحدث عندما تتعلم النموذج الذي يعتبر جيدًا للغاية عند تطبيقه على بيانات التدريب،
is training error that is too low but doesn't do well on the true error.
هو خطأ في التدريب والذي يكون منخفضًا للغاية ولكنه لا يؤثر على الخطأ الحقيقي.
Now let's preview some of these overfitting plots which we discussed
والآن دعونا نستعرض بعض من تلك الرسومات ذات التطابق المفرط
quite a lot in the regression course.
والتي ناقشناها باستفاضة في الدورة التدريبية الخاصة بالانحدار.
So, here in the x axis I'm showing the model complexity.
ولهذا، فإنني أوضح في المحور X تعقيد النموذج.
The model in the left is a very simple constant model,
ويعد النموذج، على جهة الشمال، نموذجًا ثابتًا غاية في البساطة.
while the model in the right is a crazily polynomial very high degree.
بينما النموذج على جهة اليمين هو نموذج مضطرب بحدود كثيرة ومرتفعة للغاية.
So, if you look at the training error,
ولهذا، إذا نظرت إلى الخطأ في التدريب،
when you use a constant model it doesn't do really well in the training data.
عندما استخدمت نموذج ثابت، فإنه لم يُبلي حستًا في بيانات التدريب،
But it feels this crazy high degree polynomial,
ولكنه أظهر حدود مضطربة بدرجات مرتفعة.
you might get zero training error.
وقد لا تحصل على أخطاء تدريب.
And somewhere in between, we get training error.
وفي مكان بينهما، فقد حصلنا على خطأ في التدريب
There is decreasing like that, and eventually goes to zero.
هناك انحدار يشبه ذلك، والذي يصل في النهاية إلى صفر.
So this is my training error.
ولهذا، هذا بمثابة خطأ التدريب الخاص بي،
And the problem with training error goes to zero
ووصلت المشكلة في خطأ التدريب إلى صفر،
is if you look the underlying model, it doesn't do well on other houses.
وإذا نظرت إلى النموذج الضمني، فإنه لم يُبلي حسنًا عند تطبيقه على المنازل الأخرى.
So the true error is very high when you don't have a lot of data.
ولذا، فإن الخطأ الحقيقي يكون مرتفع جدًا عند عدم وجود الكثير من البيانات.
Sorry when your models very simple.
أسف، عندما تكون نماذجك بسيطة للغاية.
But it's also very high when your models very complex.
ولكنه يكون مرتفعًًا أيضًا عندما تكون نماذجك معقدة للغاية.
And the true error function has this kind of characteristic process.
ودالة الخطأ الحقيقي بها نوع من عملية مميزة.
It goes down and then goes up.
والتي تذهب للأسفل ومن ثم للأعلى.
So this is the true error.
ولهذا، فهذا خطأ حقيقي.
So overfitting is going to happen
ولهذا، فإن التطابق المفرط
when we pick something that's too good in the training data.
يحدث عندما نقتطف شيء جيدًا للغاية في بيانات التدريب،
So it's somewhere over here, but it doesn't do well with aspect to true error.
والموجود في مكان ما هنا، ولكنه لا يُبلي حسنًا مع جانب الخطأ الحقيقي.
So in other words, you get some w hat over here that has very low training error,
وبصيغة أخرى، معك هنا جزء من Ŵ، ولكن به خطأ تدريب منخفض للغاية،
but high true error while there were exists some other certain parameters.
ولكن خطأ حقيقي مرتفع، بينما تتواجد بعض المعلمات الأساسية الأخرى.
We can call them w*, which might not have done as well in the training data, but
ويمكننا تسميتها w*، والتي ربما لم تلبي حسنًا في بيانات التدريب،
man, they did much better as performance in the true error.
ولكنها يا صديقي، قامت بالأفضل كأداء في الخطأ الحقيقي.
And so we want to try to avoid taking these highly-performant
لذا نريد أن نحاول تجنب أخذ هذه النماذج عالية الأداء
models in the training data that don't do well in the real world.
في بيانات التدريب والتي لا تحقق نتائج جيدة في العالم الحقيقي.
So we want to shift From the right here to the left to avoid overfitting.
ولهذا نحن بحاجة ان نتحرك من اليمين إلى اليسار لتجنب التطابق المفرط.
Now this was for the regression setting.
والآن وبينما كان ذلك لإعداد الانحدار،
Next we'll talk about it in the classification setting.
فإننا سنتحدث بعد ذلك فيما يتعلق بإعداد التصنيف.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]